Register of the Juliene Williams papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed Matter, 1970-1971, 1984-1986 (Box 15)
  - Periodicals, 1970-1971, 1986
    - The New American: A Weekly Review of the News & American Opinion, 1986 February 24 (Box-folder 15: 9)
    - Pottstown Mercury, 1970 June 18 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - The Prisoner of War Problem, 1970 (Box-folder 15: 11)
- Oversize Material, 1970, 1978, undated (Box 16)
  - Gordon C. Hill military awards and certificates, 1970, 1978, undated (Box-folder 16: 1)
    Contains certificates for various military awards bestowed upon Hill for his service in the Vietnam War. Each certificate includes a citation or letter describing the award. Also included is a photograph of Air Force jets in midair.
  - Distinguished Combat Wife Award certificate, undated (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - "High Flight," poem by John Gillespie Magee, Jr., undated (Box-folder 16: 2)
- Memorabilia, circa 1970-1983, undated (Box 16)
  Includes five of Hill's military medals and a Psi Omega fraternity charm.